by the way it might not be nothing there
might be nothing but dog eyes some guys
through the Nova wiki in the IRC chat I
mentioned 404 being funny as the area
code in Atlanta
notice that symbol above the 404 here
and at the other location there were
three peace symbols graffiti done to one
of the V pillars supporting the overhead
pass didn't think anything of it at the
time they weren't connected they're on
different surfaces but three P symbols
three circles they weren't joined but
three circles are who knows anyway yeah
me now and here in relation to where
this page was it's pretty much you can
see framed I don't know fine means
nothing if I was right about the other
location where the flyer was then it had
your back was to the peace symbols so I
don't know if it means anything but you
know there it is and there's a goddamn
weird phone numbers here everything's
charged with two six six well a lot of
numbers too
so yeah anyway and now later cuts